we're gonna practice Alliance dance as
much as we knew already vamos a
practicar la danse le on a stone Ellis I
promise I'm gonna just give you a brief
description of the the third was worried
I don't have a description of the zero
we're on a second
sorry second of the formulas right
estamos en el segundo nivel del mu del
Reino sin forma and I'll take you
through the whole thing again in order
okay let's go yeah sir
Janos why you are por todo el recorrido
and northern so don't worry but this
money will go through everything we've
done so far
Espinoza broke open hacer el recorrido
ptolemy as soon as Dora so let me
describe it first and then we'll try to
do it together okay
primero boy yes Alison my scripts yoni
levelling tantrums and Cervantes the
first by the way the whole thing is
called the lion stance
Toula Lomita Sugiyama la danza Leon
we're starting in the desire realm state
of mind which is like tasting cappuccino
listening to air conditioner okay and
pasamos and the rain of the sale
let's come on provider cappuccino
escuchar later conditional then we're
going to go you know through the forum
realm levels four levels look Obama seal
Sui another 15,000 us the drain on a
former focusing on our heart and focus
on El Corazon which is still has a
component of physical physicalness we're
still aware of physicalness okay yeah a
stylist I won't say most conscientious
Ella physically dad then we'll go into
the formulas formulas for formulas
meditations okay
Ramos otra vez de las Neto Sione's a
Ramos informant and the first one we did
yesterday was called la primera
Christmas in the space okay and it's
that feeling of the body is anesthetized
okay the body is numb la primera
infinite espacio finito con el
sentimiento de Klerk or post anesthesia
no awareness of form seen donde eres
Aparicio la conciencia la forma and then
we expand the mind as far as space and
you can keep going it's like if you drop
the stone in the middle of this leg and
then it would just keep going
the the Ripper would just keep going
like that y luego s Panama la mente hace
el espacio in finito como cuando Venter
soon appeared Renee Lago y las olas
expand Sivas the Las Olas continuing
continue and continue on then the second
formulas oh by the way when you go from
desire to form you compare something to
something
si en por cierto para cuando 2 passes
del rey no el deseo al Reno la forma lo
haces compare and una cosa con una otra
there's this desire or I I don't want to
listen to the air-conditioner anymore I
want to go someplace more quiet aun si
no career escuchar later commissioner
Herrera un lugar más que yo so that's
the basic idea between these rounds okay
y esta as leia Vasek allah Tran
transition train and when you get to the
end of the forum yeah you are el final
de cuarto ring and final formal
you're deep into your heart estas dentro
de Corazon and your mind feels how
should I say even the feeling of
happiness is gone your mind just feels
Haruko fat line the feelings are
flatline
incluso a ye tu mente esposa parisa el
sentimiento de la felicidad to maintain
and train on amass a turnip Lanisha the
you esta smelled and at the last part of
the forum your body is almost like
somebody gave it a shot
like numb anesthetized okay you know
time apart la la forma to corpore
astonished SEL como si stylist Anastasia
then you compare that body that physical
heart
- no no no physical logo en la siento
transition compare us as a cup of
physical as a chorus on physical my
remoten always so it's another
transition because you're comparing
where you are with where you could go
that's why you moved from the formula to
the formula y la manera que puta madre
no la forma else in forma s compare ando
una cosa con la otra la physically
reconnaissance ela physically like even
this numb body is to growth and I want
to go somewhere more subtle later ask a
stochastic where poor mr. Cordell
quality consider Corazon s demasiado
vents Ichiro Iran lugar mucho mass
appeal and the difference between the
first formless
meditation and the second formless
meditation is again a comparison Allah
if Orencia entre el primero el de reims
informally el segundo knee well as the
transition the never sought recuperación
the feeling in the first formless realm
for me it's like as I said I feel
horizontal I feel like a lake the top of
a lake and my mind is just going out in
a ripple and it's not going to stop it's
still going
el sentimiento Perriman el primero nivel
de de la maison forma es como es
horizontal is common lago y case
expanded by panocha parada expand
edition then in the second form a
theorem
okay that's where we are this morning en
el segundo nivel de dreams in forma I'm
going to take away the image of form and
I'm just gonna think about the state of
mind that's riding that image going on
you see drop everything just think
consciousness consciousness going like
this not not some kind of image of a
lake or space okay
in when you go from the first formless
realm to the second formless realm it's
because you're dissatisfied with space
and you want something more subtle and
that consciousness
sella transition the less pasión finito
not known that expand this and lock on
sense infinita to plataforma be swallow
imaginative ah de expansion podría ser
on logic as expanded pero to tennyson 15
satisfied Chaka NASA plataforma Concha
visually that case my away.he entrar en
estado inclusive masa till he was
popularly muffin cassia so la conciencia
concerns expands Eva seen a libretto
visual mental Connor calls expand Mia
okay got it
let the syrup before you drop the air
conditioner because it was too gross and
you wanted something more subtle which
was your heartbeat
primero abandon Aaron Larkin senado poor
Tara muy bien so Tyrion Algoma Sutil
lateral Corazon and now you're it gets
very subtle okay just a motion you are
dropping the image of endless space
because endless consciousness is more
cool more sub
después de general imagine del espacio
infinito la stessa Banda Nando porque la
conciencia infinita a mucho mejor mucho
mas appear and again it would take about
an hour to make this transition
yes sir esta transition table maria como
una hora so we're gonna pretend say que
vamos a fin here we're gonna visualize
we are moving from first formulas to
second formulas but actually we're
halfway in the air conditioner service
Felice are estamos en la transition del
primer nivel del station for del Rios
informa El Segundo nivel peaceful Sally
Martin are no pero cuando Ella esta
Ramos and later conditional are these
levels ago a castle stores novellas me
that he was soon on the meta no okay
don't get distracted nice triangle don't
spend all your time looking at the car
at the airport when you could be riding
home in susana's cars people cannot
Olivia no lot o en el aeropuerto condo
Korea's era to Casa de notre susana so
why are we why are we practicing them
porque porque estamos practical stuff
make the Sienese it's like if you are an
iron woman in in a colorado
competition eskimo Sierra she won the
competition
Allegan hola competition Ironman primer
lugar and border Colorado in Quito
anyway so you run in a lot of crazy
places if you want to run in a normal
place you see what I mean
you run up and down big mountains if the
race is going to be held on a small
mountain okay see para a certain train
ami ento para ganar en la superficie
normal penis ks7 tournament and east
into lugar es como montana scolaire as
you see so just for training purposes
so look for efectos and
maybe you run up and down this mountain
here even though you're gonna run a flat
race in Colorado
cinnamon solo para efectos para tener
Oman entrenamiento Tsubasa bajas en esta
Montana pero cuando la carrera save a
serene colorado Vassar una superficie
plan there's a second purpose to
practice this can you guess what also in
the propósito disasters practicas he
says seed seizes okay ELISA samia's what
a negative purpose call Estella factor
negative oh now you don't mistake it for
emptiness you see what I mean you don't
go there by accident one day and you say
oh I saw emptiness a lot of propósito
testamento seoane espera cannot confront
us no confundus s s ex perience second a
perception director la cuidad Silvia
poor accident entrar en este estado Mita
TiVo say Paz canastas perceive and
directamente lava quia or you go to some
teaching and the teacher describes form
round number three and you're like and
they call it emptiness bassam on Nancy
and Sylvester catalyst time party endo
describe a person evil the Ramos informa
it is a case Islamic weeow / - yeah
service kanaloa Sportello pray mr. king
then here then you know you can say oh
yeah I tried that I know what it is our
teacher took us there and that's not
emptiness that's just that's just a car
a fancy car and services from ESO
maestro maestro Encino yes or no is the
perception directed avocadoes
implemented and we could look at the
year I am and I think if if you practice
these nine right ten it's gonna be ten
is used as practical
can really Alvin a service and then you
go to meditation classes by anybody the
logo analyst classes Anita's she only
called Kirika Allyson Sonia what you
hear will be in in one of those ten
lessons enhances guess Cochin mister -
Darren Kavinoky noggin SSDs some some
copper starts out his summary by saying
new moon changes something Y so Kappa
and pieces so resume n what it mean yeah
these states of meditation are are still
negative states of mind they are still
linked number one this occurs closest
Estonia Ellis the minute a cien cien
cien doe nihilism limitation estas
mental as negative O's Castle vinculum
era uno del in neuron sia not a la vida
so it if you practice them a
supercilious black beacon then you can
then if you go to some weird meditation
class and they talked for a long time
about something you can you can in your
course it's not polite to say that's
just stupid mistake number three you
know see well now Atlas ami minute ASEAN
and tu mente yeah North Wales the seal
pero cuando switches like classes a CSL
roar numero tres yeah Lopez clasificado
no surprises here oh yes ask is in the
road but at least yourself you want you
won't be attracted to just doing that
yeah pero por lo menos to kill ya tienes
la enseñanza no se sentir ossetra IDO
Isola serious okay so let's meditate
let's go up to second formless iva-mos
entrar en el segundo me where the
dryness informa
I really like this babysitting
arrangement I mean most amateurs DoCoMo
sysinternals oversee address the kids
are out in the open under the beautiful
trees los ninos estan afuera en el
parque de vito they were hollow solace
and they get to play with each other for
wagon and trade shows and the parents
are listening to the class los pop
assistance couch and hola clase
that's a cool system this is my one
sister man okay here we go ready
make sure your phone is off I said what
are the guests about two cellular
[Music]
then relax your forehead la jolla frente
relax your eyelids lock apart pathos
and have a little smile la sonrisa sutil
polynyas domain method abdomin
relax your fingers a locket of zeroes
and then we'll come to a desire realm
instead of mine Alejo empezamos in el
estado mental del drain of the cell and
it's very easy we can just focus on air
conditioner assuming fossil so low
concentrations which I later conditional
and now compare that sound to the sound
of your heartbeat compare a cell to neo
con le tu corazon
then go into your heart be the net
Rennell chorus in Tula tear Corazon be
the heart did compete compete at NSA
latina notice how quiet and pleasant it
is like being at Lake xalapa it's so
quiet and pleasant compared to the noisy
Guadalajara city the quanta hello Rico
Pacifico Casta rescue master en el agua
chilapa on comparison con el tráfico
Lesya well aha
so in the second form met former
meditations the Mosin trollin evil those
Delrin informal there's no awareness of
the air conditioner anymore you know I
can see insulator conditioner and even
looking at the heartbeat and feeling it
in a strong way is gone with a mean of
observation el sentimiento a little
Corazon for taste say you know and we
are inside the heartbeat your estimate
landrum relative the body feels very
light and strong two purposes in the
movie the hero
if worthy and there's a feeling of very
pleasant to be so quiet during
sentimiento the + el estor in fantasy
lands must stay here for a few minutes
aquí que hemos unos minutos
now you think oh I'd like to go deeper
you're interested Oprah for my service
so now the pleasant feeling of the
second form level mental feeling oral
pleasure mentality n that son Donovan
dela formal that's also a kind of
destruction the mentor is try it it's
nice to be quiet the way mr. Collier
its pleasant to be quiet just plus
interest or insolence but I want to go
deeper rocky Roe you must perform the
feeling of pleasantness in the quiet is
a distraction a sensation the Placer
Dempsey lens is no instruction and I
want to go deeper then woke up upon this
earth so we're going to try to compare
the feeling of pleasure about how quiet
it is in this meditation mercy was
inventor compare our lessons I see on
the plus here del Silencio meatus yawn
compare it to a state of meditation
where there's you've gone beyond that
Pleasant feeling and now your mind is
just sort of numb compared so come
Nestor NFC antenna well-merited evil and
they went a mystic my Laura Mercier and
move into that place where they for a
third forum that certain available
during the
[Music]
no longer thinking about how nice it is
to be quiet
a savannah loss pensamientos you know
scatter veces que bueno que presenta
register incidence the body still feels
good and straight and healthy Eric where
position CTMS avian under Assad oh
listen
now we're gonna drop all feeling of the
body I've undone a total sentiment or
whirlpool the mind is already deeper
than feeling good lament a Yasu pero el
estado de saint-étienne and now we're
going to drop all sensation of the body
as if the body were Nam Baba Sawan donor
toda la sensation is Alberto Macias Thuy
Araneta cielo a form Brown number four
another four monomer of water go deeper
must perform don't forget everything
about your body settle via toll at the
purple everything is the quietness of
the mind to us lucky to element them and
there's even no feeling about it it's
just quiet in Mayan sentimiento con
respecto a circuit to estação lab yet no
emotion about it just quietly by una
emotion con respect allocated solo idea
to
now we'll move to the formless realm
intraday motion Adreno scene for me I
don't want to be limited by a body no
quiero estar limited porn cuerpo I will
send my meditation away from a single
place quiero irme metas en vivo de un
Sol de una sola localization and my
meditation will cover o space me
meditation co coral atoll Allah's path
endless space especially need sonar
expand the meditation expand a
limitation or infinitely the for me
infinite in space portal is pass
now think I don't want to be limited by
limited I don't want to be limited by
limitless space European side rocky rose
and pere milà matado con el espacio
limited kana plataforma Mita tavella's
passionated limited my mind itself is
unlimited that can be maintained as a
limiter another pend oreille honest pass
I don't need to be limited to even all
of the space there is gonna stow sentir
millimeter inclusive Porto el espacio
existing I can go beyond our place there
is no puedo here Monsieur todos los
lugares existing I can just be my mind
so la pucelle momentum limitless mine
meant a limit without reference to space
sin tener el punto and fluffy or
referential el espacio so I choose to go
to that quieter place chicas Coco and
Terrence a lugar mass silly ensues
now we'll go to formless realm number 3
directly directamente entradas in there
there's an evil Deramus inaudible
thinking about my endless mind open sir
and tu mente infinite even without
reference to endless space inclusing que
estas think la de espacio finito it's
still a distraction CSE endo no
instruction I could go deeper
whether you must profunda I could drop
thinking about my mind whether they fer
de penser any maintain I could drop
being aware of my own mind what I want
honor la conciencia me procurement and I
could go to a deeper place by entering
enormous problem nothing now we'll go
there vamos a more quiet residence you
let's go to the last formless lava a
central neural timoni where the drain is
informal at the second formless level it
was a distraction to think about my
endless mind in that ceremony where the
restriction pencil and to maintain
Vinita but at the third formless level
universe and even de la forma it was a
distraction to try to not think about my
mind when a distraction intentar no
pensaron me meant so I will go to a more
quiet place today lugar más que yellow
formless lava for we were cuatro Reynosa
follow me no more thinking about my mind
European soul and momentum and no more
trying not to think about my mind but a
tampoco intent oh no pencil in me meant
go beyond nothing deeper bus Monsieur
Ilana to where nothing was possible
anyway and lugar donde la nunca la
piscine de most quiet place in over
mascara will stay here for a few minutes
scary music unos minutos
then please come to your breath three
deep breaths
tres respirations profundas
and then you can slowly open your eyes
gentlemen Terrence office
you okay no didn't get hurt no what
happened
mystery just by itself just by itself SE
cayó el árbol secure poor see solo
who can tell me what number three was
formulas number three jimena Papa's
equality well tell me what number two
was jamey prezzi really well does that
seem Deramus informa yeah
drop drop the endless Plains hondana la
plataforma del espacio finito and go to
the endless mine is solo / - Akane
better meant infinity without comparing
it to space without without suspense in
compare our lock on el espacio
then I don't know you guys were doing so
good I thought we should just go ahead
to number three yes Donita no también se
que dije vamonos electoral tres
now what gotcha gasps gotcha they object
to the night it's the thing that
emptiness is empty our is a secure Ella
petal
Caleb acquittal niega it's the thing we
say is not there as la cosa que no está
II with the pen what is it kana pluma
case the self-existent pen yeah a pen
which could come from its own side el
objeto Jaime Ramos and avec we doll is
la pluma can exist as la pluma
exist connects campus at the upper end
existed as popular here an existing no
such thing miss turtle cosas in the
kitchen watch The Guardian in la cocina
colossal gotcha yeah
the husband who's yelling at you not
because you yelled at your kids last
week ok tonig our Oh gotcha de la cocina
sell esposo katha grita syndra's oh no
since in relation alguna con el grito
capillary assist a to sekolah semana
pasada
so that gotcha
does
exist that the Buddha always said it
like this doesn't exist never existed
can't exist Elwha de siempre lo dijo I
see a cigar or katana got an existent
that no existing mooncat Sestito no
existed in ink existed ah now somebody
who was in Si I am semester number two
who know a link a tomorrow so the end CA
solana numero dos even the professor's
Rousseau lost my instruction tell me the
difference between map and sealife
Orencia the capture of logic and the
gotcha of the path came upon BC la
diferencia entre el gotcha
de la logica Allah gotcha El Camino and
to same we talked about it do you have
let's go I'll try okay it's short answer
if it's too long it's wrong they don't
work by itself
[Music]
yeah the path doesn't work by itself
no no okay we always say two kinds of
God choice the CMAs que los tipos a
noxious Guardians something you want to
stop right God means to stop
gotcha significally okay Kira's got
significant debt an heir so one God
never existed that's a pen which comes
from its own side
I'm gotcha nunca exist yours la pluma
que viene kazoo kazoo propiedad Oh No
yeah the the link number one the
misunderstanding the pen LAN comprar
vinculum era una la la in compression de
la pluma
that's also a gotcha I gotcha
we call it a gotcha line compression de
la pluma también a song gotcha it's
something you want to stop s algo que
quieras at the net does that one exists
a castle and cinco precision in
comprehension exists a
yeah that exists yes SSE existed okay so
when you go deeper in the idea of gotcha
quando profundus is a novella gotcha
Rigby gotcha
the gotcha which we want to deny with
thinking the rig back atcha locket
rocket Ramos Mega Million Tay a loser
pensamiento the husband who just yell at
me for no reason
el espacio Chemical guitars
international woman that one never
existed as a people as possible not
exist but the idea that he is coming
from his own son
pero lay there like a circus esposo
esposo cerca de su propio lado we also
call that a gotcha the minimum says o
una gotcha but that gag shot can exist
does exist and we have to stop it
yes I gotcha what existed is she exists
Allah Thomas Illumina why are we talking
about that portal ahmo's I saw in the
study of meditation in the mystery
element ASEAN when you go through this
for when you go from desire realm to the
for forums on the bus cuando el récord
Reynard señora de los cuatro menos a la
forma and then you go from the for
formula for formless realms
he was a las cuatro dreams allah formal
scott arenas in forma
there's a guardian at each step in
colony well del recorrido a young gotcha
okay you are going you are drilling
deeper into the object
it's the spur foreign doctors must
perform DiNozzo Khatta meetha TiVo's but
in the study of meditative state of mind
when the less to your el estado mental
mental people
you are always saying oh that's that's
not subtle enough I want quieter
I want quieter siempre y una voz
interior kept estás diciendo
SOS nice vision
the suit bill yo yo quiero que se da man
Silencio so every time you move into a
different llama color captain wasn't the
only well distinto you are rejecting
something and you're saying it's Nocona
estas como refute ando algo que no
quieres algo diciendo no suficiente
venti Silencio so I want more quiet
ghetto
Marceline's so what's the first capture
we did today
what was the first thing that wasn't
quiet enough before luck or second order
so this intimate assyrians yo se ya
later conditional listening to the air
conditioners which are later
commissioner okay what about the second
one
yeah it's a wound okay yet the heartbeat
was too loud Allah to Allah for a son
Tommy fuerte from the outside there's a
windowless afuera okay so we went inside
the hardly knows my demos and reality
dough and it was nice to be so quiet
when start ANCA yeah I just gave you a
clue about the next culture yeah 30
people contract expect a la cinta gotcha
yeah you gave up you said this nice is
nice but it's too loud
but I love Allah he stay it's the
sentiment of esto aqui esta bueno stop
why not Paris de Macedo asked me to read
over I want something quieter you know
mask a yellow I don't want my mind thing
this is quiet this is nice this is nice
shut up
look at me mr. Vitiello camión está
siendo
it's just a Silencio so it's this Darwin
kiss kiss Italian a serious you telling
me how nice it is to be quiet is getting
too noisy related to mental edge
economist decision oh yes our losses
tired
silenzio harvest amar widow so then that
Pleasant feeling of the meditation
becomes Agharta y entonces en ese
momento la sensation placenta LM a Paseo
cerca Milton decoction it's something
you drop to go deeper a lot given
Donna's para perform massage so then
what happened
you okay so Sarah what was the next
thing we drop los en take care of
anonymous so we we were in a neutral
mental state estamos en esto mental
neutral neutral feeling sentimental noon
okay I give you a clue listen in a pista
but the body was still felt cool to be
in the body around the sink this is muy
bien está entre to that de cuerpo yeah
then we drop that Camino and on a MOS
how cool it feels to be in deep
physically how cool it feels to be
totally when he call it in ballet
balanced balanced uh nice and
symmetrical or something aligned yeah
okay so by the time you got the third
form Laura Rambo cuando yoga's on their
journey well del Reino la forma you told
you mind already be quiet
yells each Ottoman Turkish echo yeah
stop telling me how cool it is
yes I see me what sabroso testosteron
Silencio but you had this alignment of
the body
pero tenesmus and sassy on the Allan SEO
Nikki anywhere brother flowing well the
perp under here to cover Yendo when you
drop it
Tammy no and Donna says then the body
starts to feel your core position no
Missy like when they give you that stuff
in the dentist you know and then you
can't feel anything
yes okay mr. seal cuerpo let me call it
novocaine so think body whole body
novocaine a secret bonus this year
okay that's fourth form realm level the
mind already novocaine the feelings
already novocaine sentimiento yet the
meanest Anastasia yesterday previa
maintenance this year
then what's the gotcha when you move
from the last form realm level to the
first formless realm level well the name
should give you a clue koala koalas
koalas all gotcha cuando se la
transition del Reino de la forma alrey
no sin forma simplemente los nombres de
Lorean stay very end are una pista de lo
Calvin donas yeah why should I be
focused on one point forecaster
kinsella punto let me be focused on all
points if I messed up under me attention
please
in total respond to the less passive
okay let me expand this meditation to
all points in space become expanded
estimate Acciona todos punto del espacio
what's the connects gotcha Felicity in
the gotcha Kevin dullness platform space
why should I compare myself to space my
mine is much more endless ten space ever
was porque me day compare our con el
espacio documentas mucho mas infinita
DeLaughter pudiera ser el espacio I'll
just drop space so London area let's
pass him at the second formless llama
and it's a wound only well the Rhinos
informal I'm just in my infinite mind
story
serving me meant infinita now how to go
from that to the third formless room if
you tell me off for I'll let you go to
the bathroom si como as they say el
tercer nee well the dryness informal the
lament if Anita why should I hold
anything forgettable the info Carmen
algo
why should I even hold on to my endless
mind but Karev of the fair our most are
and focal and Amenti a momenta finita
that effort is also a distraction SAS
for so then for carton 20 infinita
también es una restriction our God
holding nothing intraday Alistair the
securing for Carmen momentum Vinita
another in in Tibetan is called Chi
young man say to young man young man
[Music]
just nothing I'm not holding anything
Jang man a poor Kapoor getting
stronger and on the main TV antenna so
there was a famous debate in Tibet in
750 listen to 1250
years ago I am from also about and
development Linus a person to cincuenta
and one teacher said in must relief Oh
formless level number three is the
direct perception of emptiness de
Mestral dijo el nivel Murad Reis Uranus
inform as the perception directed of
Aquila and if you can stay there
visitor scope as Department Sarah II you
reached nirvana
Laura's concern least a linear manner
okay that that that was a wrong idea and
and I I would gas that the result of
most meditation teachings in this world
at the best is that SF well
Mileva yo podría arrived in our open
circle Amaterasu toda la mayoría cursos
America simcha say important in el mundo
given a stack II don't don't think about
anything
nope incisional right it's hard to get
there right it's it's even it's kind of
hard even to get to that it's official
you got access tunnel is that the last
place you can go in meditation I said a
little my styling and corporación
matrice your again check this out this
is co absurd when Esther's tell me why
I'm so tired
straighten concern I've tried to design
link enter the city between China hold
something or China hold nothing and
intent re enfocar me an algo Oh intent
are a landowner really algo I'm
gonna go to a place beyond those two
choices
Boyer el lugar esta Messiah
this is oz elección opciones in Tibetan
and pivot on that level as anywhere
it's called do shame a douche amen so
yeah Medusa Medusa mean say to shame a
douche a me to shame me to shimmy not
holding anything
and also not not holding anything
no info car to maintain concentration
algo me tampoco intentar y tambien
abandon olivia de intentar abandon our a
lymph okay to maintain algo like in my
meditation and in immediate minute SEO I
don't even want to make the effort of
trying to think about nothing tampoco
quiero ser el esfuerzo the intent are no
pensaron nada
I'm going beyond boy in evil super eyes
then whatever comes up I don't care
the locusts possess no me importa the
mind tries to hold you something la
maintain 10/10 for Carson algo I'm not
there constrain the mind decides not to
order something lamenting Tintin and I
want donor algo I'm not there in Tampa
Cousteau ie
Sen Cinderella's for $7.00 algo okay
real nothing okay that's the fourth
formless okay
yes el cuarto nivel del Ramos informant
now do the Lions dance la ser la danza
de la Luna
and now it's starting to feel like a
dance right your MPs isn't it sir come
on Bai Ling you go one more versa Auto
anywhere and to find that out you have
to come back from the bathroom he para
aprender SOT ningke
so those well dispersed the koi in the
wine you okay see you in 10 15 minutes
vamos and est-ce minutos okay what
happens after the you decide not to
decide that so sir cuando se us no se D
by the way somebody asked me
le me pronto
these are the these are nine stages of
meditation from Kamala Sheila solos move
annual Azimut us in the ratings machine
but in them right now that's a ten stage
[Laughter]
these are completely different
okay so some completamente distintos
these are like getting rid of these are
good Buddhist meditations esta some
bonus neeta soong is ballistas
overcoming sleepiness para super are la
toma la mente Stettinius when you
overcoming agitation ornamental tada and
developing your tool box until your mind
is very strong either surulere to kisame
enters para fertilizer to mentee the
highest part of the chart you can see
the monkeys flying in the sky la parte
más Alta Des Moines oval and
al-mustafa London in CLO and they have
achieved shamatari K yellow garage
schemata then they join it with V pass
the passion yellow a local of Kunta
combi passion which is the direct
perception of emptiness just love it the
perception directed avocadoes
so the shemitah or the deep meditation
is the platform from which you can see
emptiness directly schemata la
meditation profunda isla plataforma
bezel on the perceivers directa mental
of Aquila now I'll tell you something
interesting while yes yes there is
something that shemitah of that monk
having very perfect meditation and
flying in the sky sa shamatari sa
manhattan Inanna perfectamente Zumba
Londo por el cielo traditionally they
say is between the air conditioner and
the sound of your heart racing ma this
isn't a traditional meant a su survey
and trail area Commission
yes Neela corazon first for lava first
part of the first form
dicen que su se en la primera parte del
Rey no la forma so that's a different
thing it's a travesty that's that's a
state of that's developing the first
part of the first phases Desiree yeah la
primera parte del primer nivel del Reino
la forma de Paz Chiana
Vibhishana means to see emptiness
directly significa perceive Edie rectum
at the lava cuidado
after you reach Samantha which is the
monk flying okay
disposal girl schemata representa
Salamanca Orlando then there's a teacher
from Burma in maestro Burma who uses the
word Vibhishana goza la palabra v
pacchiana
he used the Pali word which is the
personal the person would police hola
Pilar and alidium apology Siem Reap
asana and I I studied with this teacher
it's going just to the Economist okay
see I'm a-goin I took a long retreat
with him well he's hundred pyrrole
orokin and forty-two years ago
okay and so that's a that's a different
thing that they are mainly watching
their breath as a sunnah consists in
toluca principal mint estan haciendo
subserve arthrospira co and they are
trying to get a mind quiet in the tunnel
and never get to an amenity and he also
spoke a little bit in the class in the
course I took he spoke about suffering
also in classic a yachtie me hablo del
Sacramento so I don't know where you
would put it in in what we just studied
I think you know somewhere in the forum
love us okay you're not selling the
panacea samhitas in
context alok estamos estudiando yo creo
que en algún ellos new a little raynella
Foreman
they don't teach emptiness at all as far
as I know or correctly okay look at
yourself every personal SK and knowing
singing correctamente circle of Aquila
okay so I'm this couple days class has
not been about this I think a lot less
estos últimos Ozias no ha sido de esto
if you want to study that come to DCI
level three security area solving an ax
the C in evil dress okay so let's take
that down so we don't get confused se
que vamos a sacar no confirmed business
now we're going back to the lion stands
or vamos a tarantula Leona so what
happens why are we doing this eight no
l99 state of mind now if we count the
desirable porque estamos haciendo stro
estos no estas mentality logarithm shall
drain out the sale it's it's just to
sharpen the mind so look for a a
circular mantis Tomas brilliant they
must furtive and it's also to recognize
what's not emptiness para poder cerca
pasar con ser lo que no es la la cuidad
it's quiet
soon lugar Silencio Silencio and it's a
good karma yes someone karma why okay
mainly because you can't do any bad
comments while you're thinking about
endless space
[Music]
Karma's mentor cestas pensando en el
espacio voseo today's 8 have a good
result acaso estas Oh Johnny belliston
when resultado yeah you can be born in a
higher higher realm than human
hi well including human and higher
cheaper to pay renacer and Reina
superior color in Oman Oprah terminal
Romano clue Edo but you cannot get out
of suffering pero no puedo salir del
Elsa Colorado so Freeman they are still
in the Wheel of Life
una persona que hacer en estas medicinas
CNRS lamento so a body suffer from boys
odd uses this 8 would be Lisa's to Soto
and they go to a ninth one but I don't
know where no I can he well so we have
desire realm state of mind then the most
Alice telemental the runner the sale
then you have for form RAM state of mind
illa godinez Quatro estas mentally the
Rinella forma then you have for formless
realm state of mind
ah tres Quatro dealt in forma and then a
body sufferer will on the first body
sample level although there's a debate
about that I'll body servant supremely
well there was advocated about the
conspiratorial so they will go through
the nine really right recorder lost my
way and then they will do something at
the end yell final hacer algo after
drilling down down down down under
después de star perfer Ando they were
going to what we call cocaine your jokes
a cocaine
go up a young Duke d'Anjou golpe golpe
Nam Joo young Duke so go pay young Duke
the word means meditation on cessations
stopping meditation on stopping la
palabra significant asean in las seis
asean a los zetas and para tener a loop
then there's two exponential evasion
Devin Segundo motivation number nine
two different kinds of meditation Ellen
and evil no way sir dos tipos de Medici
own if you have a lower motivation not
Bodhisattva okay see tienes una
motivation menorca male voice agua when
you reach the ninth one a llegar al no a
no-go pain yong-jo cessation meditation
on the u.s. a Lama Tashi on the la
estación
all of your feelings and sensations
those two sentimiento see census illness
and all of your thought process it was
momentous mentalis de cemento suspended
temporarily second suspended owes
temporal mental
okay and then they mistake this for a
important goal that oh yeah key with
chicken tests confirm the cone automate
important why does it happen
porque su CSO cuz you've been quiet and
you've been nice for costello and cilia
yes and also those seeds use as a media
caused you to reach the super peaceful
place towson general este lugar tom
Pacifico where your feelings stop than
the yard to sentimiento certain and your
thought process stop it was pensamientos
tummy so if you're not a body start
better see to marry somebody sad when
you hang out there the girl saying what
happens after that gets their disposal
those seeds we're out it's a semi your
tonsils Gaston then you pop out you
can't stay there because the seeds were
yellow what the salads a ye poor cannot
oppose my husband - sorry poor case a
cavernous amigas and then normally you
go to a lower berth okay you just
possess or normalmente there was some
training for your okay
so that kind of cessation meditation is
not something we want to do we want we
don't want to reach us meditation where
we're not thinking about any
II no queremos lograr allocative of them
the young our own estimate even Elkhorn
opens emotional now here's how we
explain a bodhisattva cessation
meditation okay
yes Alex plication de l'année passée
under cessation the UN Bodhisattva and
for Stanley I took this from a lama
called Sarah Jetson cheeky guns and
Sarah Jetson Chuck accountant yesterday
esto está texture viene one lamasery
Jetson cheeky Gilson there's too cheeky
gun sense i those cheeky cousins one is
the first pension number el lunes el
primer panchen lama this is not that
work but as the no assessing this one is
the most famous textbook apart from
Sarah it's textbook writer Thomas famoso
a Sarah and he was born in 1469 Nacional
mid cuatro Vientos is something new a
way he passed away in 1546 Amorian milk
in en tus : places his student wrote the
textbooks for my monastery so as to the
ante trehalose liberals a texture any
ministerio okay here's his definition i
just a su definition
oh no teacher go pain Yamaguchi you
wanna find us you guys you can search
for B Y space B Y space No
okay let's just go got it
yeah that's it okay on our cheek open yo
yo yo Gina why did they call it
sensation meditation for kala jamun
meta-analysis Asian for bodhisattva me
it does endure this is a sea imperiled
was very sad was sad to pay a situation
for example let's take the emptiness
meditation of a bodhisattva on the sixth
bodhisattva normal for example
Omotesando bodhisattva sobre la vaca NL
section evil voice alba killer go
premium GOP guilt in your day there's a
reason why we call it sensation
meditation I am NOT the Opera quality
I'm Amita sein de la salle de la
secession then you know the punchline
what they call cessation here is
emptiness a lo que la German secession
and nest and esta text OS a lava Cuidad
and they are meditating on that
emptiness Eastern a tenderness of a
Cuidad and that's why we call cessation
meditation reported as the motive upper
quarter yama meditation an obsessive
cessation what stopped okay as long as a
to one the panda came from its own side
la pluma Covino this versus popular
okay got it int and iran now that in the
lions dance meditation in Omotesando
liliana that's where you park after the
fourth formless realm meditation IES on
detest Acciona disposal Amita see on del
cuarto nivel del dryness informal here
you're like a lion less commonly on you
are showing off your power most render
to pull a look I can do this one I can
do this one I can do this one I can do
this one all these many eight nine
states of mind whether generalist
developmentally still trustee otro the
first one I know I really kind of just
showing off you know look I can I could
do air conditioner plus primero Sandra
Lee Iacocca's prosimian Seema poorest
animal Easton I can I can do herby see
your personality el corazon I can also
do in the space tambien para austin el
espacio finito
I could do nothing Lana absolutely I can
do neither something no nothing you know
tambien para ser la laaa an absolutist
mean like enormous forces in history but
after all those mental meditation
strengthening exercises pero después de
certeau vs jose Fortaleza me Antonio
Marita TiVo I used the instrument for
something important with the little
instrumental / algo importante I think
about the pen being so in la pluma and
does the pen come from a sunshine a casa
la pluma Venus does this propiedad oh
okay
in terms of that the okay this guy has
five ghost DC I talked about five goals
BCI tiene Cinco metas
first one la primera financial freedom
Libertad financiero independencia okay I
don't want to get rich no no quiero ser
muy Rico but my goal is to not think
about money I don't want to waste my
time thinking about money
Yo no quiero ser Rico pero not a poco
key repair the improvements and onl be
mayor I want the money to show up in my
backpack
yeah you can kill dinero para esta mi
mochila so it's there when I want to buy
something but I guess they econ do
comprar algo but I don't want to think
about I don't want to waste my life
thinking about money but are you know
kilo despair easier maybe depends on
dinelli man worry about money or start
occupy freedom assertive at that Finan
Sierra
okay number two memory loss yeah I would
like to have nice relationships see the
chemos wanna relatio nice okay it's
lonely to be rich and not have friends
or family or partner yes a synthesis
mucho la Sierra Rico Parra no tienes
amigos operation familia and I would
like to be healthy you know Esther
Esther Sano I would like to feel energy
of a young person guaranteed love
Italian :
you know there are many rich people who
used up their body to get their money by
Mucha gente piensa Rica Tiago todos
estos super popper up tener dinero they
wanted to buy and what's that cars got
no the other one no yeah the other one
by that same person
now there's another one Maserati okay
yeah
lots of males muchos hombres in their
hormone period from 15 to 96 cuando está
en su período de Cumbre or Monell desde
los Kings hasta las Ventas in San Jose
they think I want to get a mess around
you know being Sankyo Maserati then all
the girls will like me but I see you
stiletto a las chicas so they work work
work hace que trabajan Trahan trova they
have officer they have heart problems
the missing a tener problemas Cariocas
for Sara's finally make enough money to
get a Maserati sense efficiently naropa
comparison Maserati and then they walked
the Maserati like this yellow Camino
nozzle Maserati I see none of the girls
wants to go in their Maserati una de las
chicas perimeter second a single
Maserati so oftentimes we use up our
strength to to get money which asbestos
was a Philly Simoes mastropiero fuerza
pair up Tanner venero
and a person with money but no physical
strength is is sad thing una persona con
dinero person for sophistical streets
algo Tristan so we'd like to have good
physical health
se que todos que hemos salud physica
those are outside things so those are
some causes experiments inside we would
like yeah peaceful mind dentro and por
dentro nos gusta a tener una
when text and pass basment Anna like
were meditating all the time
Thomas's to V Ramos merit under 30
important somebody says something to us
angry again
DeSalvo
I shall go mono ni okay II to direction
as a seem there's a bad traffic
I know traffic oh okay nothing makes you
upset
not the molesta then to have those four
for yourself then le SS Quatro causes
one asperity and live around many many
people who don't have any of them at all
BV de meillan
the muchas personas cannot even has been
busy honest it's lonely with the CNT is
in the solo it's like going to eat in a
big restaurant by yourself
Eskimo condo song grand restaurant 100
commerce solo there's a restaurant me
and we go to in Scottsdale this is a
rich part of Phoenix high-end restaurant
are koala must be your and Scott's
telcos lapatinib elephant Erica Phoenix
and you can see these wealthy divorced
people well as well as toss me your
narrative or cielos who don't want to
cook cannot get another cocina they come
and spend like hundred dollars for
dinner they order their dinner there
every day serbian banana cenar is august
ancienne dollars even ayatollah notches
and sinner and they're super lonely
understand personas and you can feel it
two percent if social era so to to enjoy
all those things by yourself a ce que
mis frutas esas cosas están de solo and
other people don't have them he work at
res personas not even know last tienen
it's just not fun there's no zipper pedo
so the faith call and like intimate
[Music]
spreading to other people share with
other people compare dear con todos a
mass what's the best way la mejor manera
pass area so koalas yeah get the first
for yourself
yes la grotta near los cuatro primero
stew and then people will ask you how
you how did you do that power how did
you do
elephant appellant Arpaio my sister so
you don't have to put up an
advertisement for your teaching - not in
escape on a policy at parado classy
people will come because you you got
what they were see will accept elegant
even DRA too classy for cat up to Easter
look at careers why am I talking about
all this poor candidate olesco the
reason to go to this ninth or this 10th
state of mind la razón motivo para esta
nova know near almaty violence early on
the reason to see emptiness directly el
décimo la razón para persevere
directamente lava cuidado
this is the way to achieve this focus
okay Esther's Naaman era para lograr la
Cinco metas so if someone teach you some
spiritual path salient and signal won't
come in a spirit world especially if
they say I'm going to teach you
emptiness especially mantasy Teresa - in
Senora cerca de Aquila then they teach
you to stop thinking they teach you
formulas numbers formulas number three
right stop thinking tanzania dakara
pants are Al nivel del rey knows informa
numero tres will it bring you those
Fargo's
a castle sturdiness and he went a local
general as a cinco metas no opposite
nature love merciful by the way that the
karmic result of doing those eight as as
a spiritual practice el resultado Cara
Miko the way serozha so Giacomo
practical spiritual I'll show you on my
phone
say la soie mostrar and me telephone
hang on
I just have this is the most frightening
moment in the modern person's life el
momento cuando mastiha susta soy pilar
las personas del lado y condo Meza
sustenance cuando encuentran subcellular
actually is here okay the Kirov hecho
why did I do that porque se so the
karmic result of these 8 meditations is
you become forgetful el resultado karmic
o de hacer esto samhitas unisys Elvia
todo you lose your car keys
so the villainous javis you can't find
your phone contrast with the left oh no
you can't you walk halfway through the
room and you stop because you can't
remember where you're going John Brady
and me we call it a senior moment senior
by the way if you're forgetful it
doesn't mean you are meditating a lot ok
no significa que tengo mucho but if you
just do those spaced out meditation
seasonal to SSSs metas Yanis on the page
there when Donna stole the karmic result
resultado Carmichael is that you you
lose things you become forgetful so the
billion esposa settle vida so it doesn't
help you get these five ghosts
okay yes or no tell you de a lograr la
Cinco metas no connection to the five
ghost no tell you a connect our gonna
sink you metas
waste of time Asuna period tiempo okay
cool
so when a body suffer does the dance of
the lion hace que cuando bodhisattvas la
danza de la leona the first eight step
the first nine right if you count the
air conditioner las Primera's no ever
see cuentas el el reino de salario
comisionado it's just kind of a mental
warmer a solo mentoring a mental mental
in Kelantan en toe and they're showing
off like those jet pilots who do you
know we have a friend John Foley yes
it's always Tennessee Kumarasamy and no
kimonos pilato's a jet come on then
Astra me go John Foley
he flew he was one of the pilots in Top
Gun and for another los pilotos and a
película Top Gun you know and they do
all these things you know like that
see it's like that okay you are just you
are just exercising your mind
that's a solar car safer cheaper to
maintain okay when you're finished with
all of those donor meditations when the
terminus Colossus has meant as soon as
the okay so pan dulce
sweet sugar I could tell you attracted
to them everyone told me case law has
such a great classic internet Rayados
estas many potato no no mijo when a
classic it will say classic those states
of mind are like sugar they're they're
addicting SSS tells me that he was on
como el azucar elect evils because
they're very quiet they're very pleasant
concealing COC Pleasant arrows but
they're not go okay pero no Sona meta
finale the goal of a fighter plane you
know this guy is very nice John Foley is
very sweet guy John Foley sniper tsunami
went on the whole scene he got
doctorate in the Senate right the
Congress of Mexico dressy on doctor
honoris causa names in a la república de
Mexico because he did all these things
you know for de Soto sisters causes but
the real purpose of his airplane
arrow propósito de servian is to kill
people he told me he was sent during the
Kuwait maybe cook a firm yellow durante
la guerra I said did you ever kill
anybody
preguntas he had when I was medallion
and he said well gosh la they sent me on
a mission
bueno que también en la misión these
small fishermen both were dropping mines
in the water to to blow up the American
ships Janos pequeños barkos pescadores
que stomping in Donna's Mina's flotantes
en el Mar para destroyed los arcos
Americanos so they got instructions on
you know take off if you see these small
fishing boats kill them sink them
Asakura Severinus Ordonez's superiores
Casey yeah no no estos barkos less
despair and he lost 3 Aaron and they
don't really know which ones are
dropping the mines or not pero no
civilian qual de estos Barco Serrano's
que estan pony and Ola swarm las niñas
flotantes mean you know he's like yes
sir you know you know because he's they
fly the path of allah and he saw a board
you know if you embark on and he go over
to check you know a person similar work
o para para where the guys like waving
to
salut da da da he turns around he gets
ready no in ptosis say Volterra para
estar listo para él dispara
and then they got a radio announcement
you know what I see I'm in support
the word is finished everybody stop
restart por favor yeah the same mission
abort abort a mission that is karma
sweet guy but our goal is not stuff
Parramatta is not an ear nose we learn
all these meditation tricks you know
nosotros appengine demos todos estos a
Villa de as Moneta Tevas do we have to
blow up what eaten a mosque is purely
the street okay yeah the gotcha
tenemos que decir la gotcha the pain
that comes from its own time link
impression de la pluma que viene de su
propio lado the husband who's yelling at
you who is not your fault el espacio
category ta cannot be any relation con
lo que haces okay that one we have to
blow up and say there's like a tenemos
curse true okay
and these exercises these eight nine
exercises estas otro on wherever si cos
they help you blow up they help you in
your mission
the plane is faster the UN and to
mention Ferguson que el avión by a mucho
más rápido okay cool
especially no so tomorrow we'll do one
last meditation when you're not
emotional team emeritus Yan will go
through all eight I said aramis hundred
Correa por las ocho will go to number
nine yo garam masala novena then we come
back down
Larisa Ramos you blow up the enemy and
then on the way home you just show off
you know me destroy yes Elena me go
yo regresa casa de la passes pursue me
no see no crevasse
most random and that's not the end of
the lion stance yes and no es el fin de
laranja Liliana if you wanna do the post
lion stance
si quieres estudiar lokasya después de
la la la Leona there's a traditional
exercise after you come down you never
cease your traditional despues they were
high and we'll talk about that tomorrow
Tammy nella Ramos esta mañana okay so
the dancing is not just to go up to 8
then 9 then come back down to eight
that's that's like the main dance but
there's more la la Senora solo records
we're a cinder loss Oh Joanie village a
girl know when you log over her I'm
dispersed a mass